lination.com 2010-11-25

# Privacy Policy | Lination

The following is Lination.com’s Privacy Policy. It was last updated 19th September 2009.

1\. No personal data collected will be distributed to a 3rd party except where necessary to complete the task required for this website (ie the data must be sent along Internet connections and be stored at a datacenter) or where required to do so by law.

2\. All data you post on the blog, comments or forum section (including your name) is available to the general public. If you are not comfortable using your real name you are able to use an alias.

3\. This website uses cookies and web beacons for the login and ad serving process. The ad serving cookies and web beacons do not include any personal data. The login cookies contain personal data which are subject to clause 1.

4\. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html "http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html").

5\. All your personal data will be deleted ASAP from this website upon a verified request. No data you have posted on the blog, comments or forum sections can be deleted.

6\. This privacy policy may be modified from time to time without notice.
